=My Sweet Professor= =Episode 8=
= أستاذي الحلو = = الحلقة 8 =
Hey.
يا.
You're also here for lunch?
أنت أيضا هنا لتناول طعام الغداء؟
No, I'm going to another restaurant.
لا ، أنا ذاهب إلى مطعم آخر.
Wait.
انتظر.
Don't.
لا.
Since you're already here,
بما أنك هنا بالفعل ،
let's eat together.
دعونا نأكل معا.
You took the only parking space left here.
لقد أخذت مكان وقوف السيارات الوحيد المتبقي هنا.
Don't worry.
لا تقلق.
I'll fix it for you.
سوف أصلحه لك.
What are you doing?
ماذا تفعل؟
Dig in.
حفر في.
Mm.
مم.
It still tastes the same.
لا يزال طعمه هو نفسه.
Did you give him the drink?
هل أعطيته الشراب؟
I did.
فعلتُ.
But why he didn't have any response?
لكن لماذا لم يكن لديه أي رد؟
What response can he have?
ما هو الرد الذي يمكنه الحصول عليه؟
Could you help me one more time?
هل يمكنك مساعدتي مرة أخرى؟
How?
كيف؟
Let's have dinner together tomorrow night.
دعونا نتناول العشاء معا غدا مساء.
What do you think?
ماذا تعتقد؟
The three of us?
ثلاثتنا؟
Of course.
بالطبع.
Fine.
بخير.
Take it.
خذها.
Put it there.
ضعها هناك.
What?
ماذا؟
When Huo Shang comes, you let him sit here.
عندما يأتي Huo Shang ، دعه يجلس هنا.
Do you get it?
هل حصلت عليه؟
You're using a trick.
أنت تستخدم خدعة.
This is nothing.
هذا لا شيء.
When he gets here,
عندما يصل إلى هنا ،
I'll have physical contact with him.
سآخذ اتصال جسدي معه.
I'll
مريض
lean over like this.
يتكئ على مثل هذا.
If he doesn't reject it,
إذا لم يرفضها ،
that means I stand a chance.
هذا يعني أن لدي فرصة.
Hi.
أهلاً.
There you are.
ها أنت ذا.
Sit here.
اجلس هنا.
Here.
هنا.
Thanks.
شكرًا.
I ordered your favorite hard-boiled egg, medium rare.
طلبت البيض المسلوق المفضل لديك ، متوسط ​​الندرة.
Isn't it a soft-boiled egg?
أليست بيضة مسلوقة؟
Do you have much homework?
هل لديك الكثير من الواجبات المنزلية؟
Yes.
نعم.
It's been tiring.
لقد كان متعبًا.
You also have lots of homework, right?
لديك أيضًا الكثير من الواجبات المنزلية ، أليس كذلك؟
Mm.
مم.
A lot.
كثيراً.
I'm very tired.
أنا متعب جدا.
Why don't you eat?
لماذا لا تأكل
Come on.
هيا.
Ah.
آه.
I'm eating.
أنا آكل.
Let's go.
لنذهب.
The exam is coming.
الامتحان قادم.
Let's relax a bit.
دعونا نسترخي قليلا.
Why don't we
لماذا لا نفعل
go to the park this weekend?
اذهب الى الحديقة في نهاية هذا الاسبوع؟
How does it sound?
كيف يبدو صوته؟
Good.
جيد.
We're all friends.
نحن جميعًا أصدقاء.
Let's go together.
لنذهب معا.
Huo Shang, let's ride the ferris wheel together.
هوه شانغ ، دعنا نركب عجلة فيريس معًا.
Gao Yuan.
جاو يوان.
Gao Yuan's afraid of heights.
يخاف قاو يوان من المرتفعات.
He can't go.
لا يمكنه الذهاب.
Yeah, I'm afraid of heights.
نعم ، أنا خائف من المرتفعات.
You guys go.
انتم يا رفاق اذهبوا.
I'm also afraid of heights.
أنا أيضا خائف من المرتفعات.
Maybe you could go alone.
ربما يمكنك الذهاب بمفردك.
We'll wait here for you.
سننتظر هنا من أجلك.
Neither of you is going.
لا أحد منكم ذاهب.
Then I'm not going.
ثم لن أذهب.
It's fine, just go.
لا بأس ، فقط اذهب.
We'll wait for you.
سننتظرك.
OK.
نعم.
I'm going then.
انا ذاهب بعد ذلك.
Bye.
وداعا.
Who's it?
من هو؟
You want to get beaten?
تريد أن تتعرض للضرب؟
Run!
يجري!
Stop there!
توقف هناك!
Go get them.
اذهب واحضرهم.
Where are they?
أين هم؟
I saw them running that way.
رأيتهم يركضون بهذه الطريقة.
Let's go.
لنذهب.
Oh.
أوه.
You hurt the man.
لقد جرحت الرجل.
Why did you make me run with you?
لماذا جعلتني أركض معك؟
Idiot.
غبي.
Because we're a team.
لأننا فريق.
If I were you,
لو كنت مكانك،
I'd just fight them.
كنت سأقاتلهم فقط.
I wouldn't have run if it wasn't for you.
لم أكن لأجري لولاك.
I'm afraid they'd hit you.
أخشى أن يضربوك.
- Oh, no!
- أوه لا!  - أوه لا!
- Liang Qi!
- ليانغ تشي! - ليانغ تشي!
Where have you been?
أين كنت؟
I've been waiting for you guys.
كنت في انتظاركم يا رفاق.
Hurry and eat.
على عجل وتناول الطعام.
Thanks for your treat.
شكرا على علاجك.
I... will see you around.
أنا سوف نراكم حولها.
Hey.
يا.
I'm always around you.
أنا دائما بجوارك.
Where's my car?
أين سيارتي؟
=My Sweet Professor=
= أستاذي الحلو =